Chiok Wei Wen Gabriel

Game Development Undergraduate

(+65) 9178 8862 | gabrielchiok@hotmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/gabriel-chiok-418538152

Aspiring Game Programmer

Dedicated and proactive game development student with hands-on experience in crafting games for Android and PC using Unity. Experience with C/C++ and C# programming. Recognized for strong teamwork capabilities and communication skills with different team members. Demonstrated leadership qualities in leading and managing game projects. Committed to continuous learning and creating great game experiences for players.

Skills

Languages: English(Native)

Programming Languages: C/C++, C#

API and Tools: Mono, RTTR, RapidJSON, Newtonsoft.JSON, Unity, Github

Soft Skills: Teamwork, Leadership, Proactive, Committed

Work Experience

DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore | Teaching Assistant

Sep 2022 - Apr 2023

Worked at the Academic Support Center to assist students with the C/C++ modules and the Game Implementation Techniques module.

gumi Asia | Quality Assurance Intern

Nov 2018 - Feb 2019

- Tested new characters, levels, quests, events, story and gacha system from Version 3.31 to Version 3.43 for Final Fantasy Brave Exvius
- Appointed as Head Intern, in charge of several administration tasks and representative of all the interns from Temasek Polytechnic

Education

DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore

Sep 2021 - Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science in Interactive Media and Game Development

Provost's List AY 2022/2023

Temasek Polytechnic

Apr 2016 - Apr 2019

Diploma with Merit in Game Design & Development

- Completed the Diploma Plus Program with a certificate in Innovation and Entrepreneurship
- Director's List AY 2016/2017

Projects

Skew Sep 2023 - Apr 2024

- Managed a group of 15 to create a 3D custom engine and a hack and slash game.
- Primary role is the Producer, ensuring that all team members progress are on track and deadlines are met.
- Secondary roles include the integration of C# Scripting, JSON Serialisation into the custom made engine and also gameplay programming for the game

Haru - A Tale of Remembrance

Sep 2022 - Apr 2023

- Worked in a group of 8 to create a 2D custom engine and a narrative puzzle game.
- Primary role is the integration of C# Scripting and JSON Serialisation into the custom made engine.
- Secondary role is the Gameplay Programmer and Gameplay Designer for the game.

Blast Off Far Away

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

- Released on Steam and Itch.io, the game is a 2D arcade game created in a team of 5 using a school provided framework.
- Primary role is the creation of the enemy AI, level systems and procedural planets and item spawning.

Waterslide VR Jul 2018 - Oct 2018

- Featured at Temasek Polytechnic's InfoTech Day 2019 and Downtown East 30th Anniversary.
- Managed a team of 5 in Unity to create a VR game to promote Wild Wild Wet based on commission by NTUC.
- Primary role was the creation of the simulation of the water slide and creation of several mini-games.

Tale of Gimcynn Apr 2018 - Jun 2018

- Worked in a team of 3 in Unity to create a 2D mobile game for Android devices.
- Worked on the procedural dungeon, enemy AI, tower defense, level and wave systems

Awards

Innolympics 2021

Second Runner Up

Temasek Polytechnics Game Jam 2018

Winner

Edusave Certificate of Academic Achievement 2017 - 2019